# JESSE LI

△ Boise, ID | ☑ JesseLiCloud@gmail.com | ② 208-957-4157

## **EDUCATION**

B.A in Business Administration Gonzaga University August 2013 - March 2017

-Management Information Systems (MIS), Operations, Finance

-GPA: 3.62

## **Relevant Courses**

- -Database Management: SQL, Data Modeling
- -Information Systems Analysis and Design: Software development life cycle
- -Problem Solving and Programming Techniques: Algorithms
- -Harvard's CS50: Introduction to Computer Science: C, Python, SQL, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

#### **SKILLS**

- -Python (Django)
- -Visual Basic.NET
- -HTML/CSS
- -Git

-C

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

Highly motivated problem solver with over two years of software development experience working with US government agencies. Experienced in writing SQL queries, recreating/developing solutions for software bugs, and working closely with clients to understand and satisfy business needs. In addition to this, I've developed software solutions to cut down on repetitive employee tasks, automating 90 minutes of daily work in my most recent position.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Online Personal Trainer**

Justin Bauer Fitness - Remote January 2022 - current

- Built an app using Python and Django to create an ETL solution that automated large amounts of employee research tasks.
- Experience webscraping data with Selenium to send API requests to third party SaaS applications.
- Generated client reports that took this information, organized it in a user friendly GUI, and created client recommendations using data algorithms.
- Experience working remotely in small teams and communicating with over +25 clients on a daily basis.

# Software Developer

Fast Enterprises - Columbia, South Carolina June 2017 - July 2019

- Developed, tested, and implemented front-end software solutions using Visual Basic.NET for internal business users and for the South Carolina taxpayer website.
- Developed reports, data fix scripts, and optimized SQL queries using MS SQL Server.
- Responsible for fixing front and back-end bugs spread across over 30 different subsystems.
- Collaborated with internal teams and stakeholders to create optimal solutions for business problems.